pricegoto.com 2014-11-10

# Privacy Policy

This document was last updated on April 24, 2014

**INTRODUCTION**

This Privacy Policy tells you the types of information we collect when you use our Sites or Services, how we use that information, and the   
instances in which we share your information.

This web site PriceGoto.com (“Site”) owned and controlled by Tigers Network Corp. (“Tigers Network Corp”, “we”, or “us”). Please note that   
this Privacy Statement applies solely to our Site. and not to websites maintained by other entities to which we may link. By using our Site, you are agreeing to the practices described in this policy.

**I. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  
We collect two kinds of information related to you: (a) Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”); and (b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”).

(a) Personally Identifiable Information: PII includes any information that identifies you as person. We collect your PII when you choose to register with us or when you choose to participate in an interactive feature of our Sites such as a review, survey or promotion. You may: (a) provide your name, mail/shipping address, email address, and phone number when registering with our Sites or in connection with a contest entry; (b) provide certain demographic information about you (e.g., age, gender, shopping interests and preferences, etc.) when participating in a survey or poll; or (c) post a general comment and/or recommendation on our Sites.

(b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information: Non-PII is any information that does not identify you as a person including PII which has been rendered anonymous. We obtain non-PII either separately or together with your PII as described above. We collect certain non-PII from you when you access our Sites including IP addresses and information relating to your browser, operating system, ISP, the third party website from which your visit originated and how you use our Sites such as the web pages you visit, and the duration of your visits.

**II. HOW WE USE & SHARE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
PII and Non-PII is used to provide, or improve, our Sites and Services to you and to carry out your requests, respond to your inquiries, better serve you and understand your needs, or is used in other ways naturally associated with the circumstances in which you provided the information.

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**III. COOKIES AND PREFERENCE BASED ADVERTISING**  
"Cookies" are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web site. We may use first-party or third-party cookies, web beacons, web bugs or action tags (a) to customize and improve your use of the Service and (b) to inform, optimize, and serve ads (at this website or through third-parties at other websites) based on your activity at this website. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Service, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. We do not use cookies to automatically retrieve PII from your computer without your knowledge.

**IV. SALE OF BUSINESS AND DISCLOSURE BY LAW**  
(a) Business Transactions: In the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution, or transfer of part of the business, trade or assets of this website, all Information collected about you via this Site may be sold, assigned, or transferred to the party acquiring all or substantially all of the equity or assets or business of this website. Subject to your election to opt out as described below, by using this Site, you consent to the sale and transfer of your information as described in this paragraph.

(b) Required disclosures: We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Site.

**V. SECURITY OF INFORMATION**  
We employ reasonable measures to ensure the security of all information and we routinely evaluate our practices to identify security threats or opportunities for the improvement of our services. No transmission of information is guaranteed to be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise data security. You acknowledge and agree to assume this risk when communicating with us.

**VI. CHILDREN**  
We have no intention of collecting PII from children under the age of 13. When we become aware that PII from a child under 13 has been collected without such child's parent or guardian's consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**VII. REVISIONS**  
Tigers Network Corp has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.  
if you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us. To Contact Us, [Click Here](http://pricegoto.com/contacts/)

This document was last updated on April 24, 2014
